{
    "subject": "resource/The_Toilers_and_the_Wayfarers",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/isPrimaryTopicOf",
    "object": "http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/The_Toilers_and_the_Wayfarers",
    "human_readable": "The Toilers and the Wayfarers is the primary topic of The Toilers and the Wayfarers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9752885699272156,
            "question": "What is the primary topic of the book 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9241626858711243,
            "question": "Who are some of the main characters in 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8800473809242249,
            "question": "What is the setting of 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8631345629692078,
            "question": "What are some key themes explored in 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.737445056438446,
            "question": "What genre does 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7273496985435486,
            "question": "Are there any other notable works by the author of 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7099334597587585,
            "question": "How has 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers' been received by critics and readers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6627326011657715,
            "question": "What time period is depicted in 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6580231189727783,
            "question": "Who wrote the book 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6551026701927185,
            "question": "What is the overall tone or mood of 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Toilers and the Wayfarers is the primary topic of The Toilers and the Wayfarers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2934_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who wrote the book 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2934_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What time period is depicted in 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2934_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How has 'The Toilers and the Wayfarers' been received by critics and readers?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2934_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2934_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\nThe document titled \"The Toilers and the Wayfarers\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2934/re-ranker-msmarco/1.txt) mentions that the film is directed by Keith Froelich and stars Matt Kemp, Ralf Schirg, and Andrew Woodhouse. The document \"Through a Queer Lens\" (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2934/re-ranker-msmarco/30.txt) states that one of the themes explored in Keith Froelich\u2019s The Toilers and the Wayfarers is about being an outcast from society and community. These pieces support that \"The Toilers and the Wayfarers\" is indeed the primary topic of the film with the same title, thus the answer is 'yes'."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}